# ELLIRAYNAI

## FULLSTACK/JAVASCRIPT DEVELOPER

# CONTACT

+1 647 996 7420

elli@elliraynai.com

636 Danforth Ave, Toronto, M4K1R3

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/

elliraynai.com

github.com/eraynai

## PROFILE

I am a full stack developer with advertising agency experience. My coding journey began with building interactive and engaging experiences in VR/AR. From there I began experimenting with the web, and fell in love with development. I have a passion for building applications, user interfaces, and working collaboratively in a team to make the best possible product.

# SKILLS

#### **TECHNICAL**

JavaScript

HTML

CSS

React Express

NodeJS

MongoDB

Vue

Django

PostgreSQL

Python

Docker

# EDUCATION

Nucamp Bootcamp Backend, SQL, and DevOps with Python March 2022 - July 2022

Software Engineering Immersive General Assembly

May 2021 - August 2021

Interaction Design and Development George Brown College September 2018 - April 2021

## WORK EXPERIENCE

# Front End Developer

Armstrong Partnership | November 2021 - Present

 As part of Armstrong Partnership's digital team, I collaborate with designers to turn their designs into interactive microsites utilizing vanilla JavaScript, HTML, and CSS. I am also responsible for building and updating pages in Adobe Experience Manager as well as building HTML emails under very tight timelines on a consistent basis. Of note, I was tasked to implement a solution to track html5 video metrics in google analytics.

## **Creative Technologist Intern**

No Fixed Address | January 2021 - April 2021

• As part of the creative technologist team I was given the opportunity to build the front end of a microsite utilizing the Vue.js technology stack. I accessed both the YouTube API and Twitter API in order to customize the experience for the user. More specifically, I was able to control how video was displayed on the site as well as give the ability for the user to pre-populate a tweet directly from the page. The site was built and deployed in a very short amount of time and won many notable awards.

## **AR Designer**

Snap | October 2020 - December 2020

- Participated in the Snap AR residency based on the my pitch for a machine learning experience called 'Nourish'
- Responsible for creative direction, user flows, concept designs, motion capture animation for 3D models, and programming interactions in JavaScript

### **Interaction Designer**

Cream Productions | May 2020 - August 2020

- Designed and delivered a coherent vision for a casual VR game
- · Conducted user interviews, competitive landscape analysis, and personas
- Built the game storyline, mechanics, and level design in collaboration with the development team